.
All you yeah, you know, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, you know, yeah.
Justdraw the most evil soul into the world.
to do the best.
Take it off
Let me see the hell is that you're going
So I can't be good, that I'm going
Hard runしてく 人生の thoughts
I'm going to die 支配し
Don't move
You're right when all is good
You're right, it's gonna break
Time and finishして 時はもう満ちた
We're shooting oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah
So 結晶とした光を 今こそ解放そう
So 覚醒と栄光のそう
核心と運命を始めよう
I made boom boom in my diapy
And some wee wee
Aw thank you
Are you going to change me too
Not now
We'll have to wait
Take another look at his special skills
Okay
Those aren't special
They're ridiculous
This explains why he couldn't leave the capital
Father!
Father I'm here!
Oh Julie!
I miss you so much!
Can you change me?
Oh!
Stop staring you fools!
Kill any remaining enemies!
Or tend to our wounded!
Ma'am!
Yes ma'am!
I beat them but now I'm hitty bitty
Please try to calm down father
If you're a naughty boy the monsters will come back
Monsters are scary
What are you gawking at?
Your dad is just the cutest little baby is all
This is a curse from the demon lord
It's in no way cute
A curse?
I'm scared!
Pick me up!
What else can you tell me about the curse?
Listen I've got my hands full now
But meet me at the castle in two hours
Sure guess we'll see you then
Let's investigate the town in the meantime
I'm sure someone else would know more than this idiot
What'd you say?
Yeah I think we'd better go see ya
Landlocked fish right here
We got deals deep in sheep
Warmaster special five for now
Here's our man the Warmaster
I'm guessing they don't know about the whole babification thing going on
I wouldn't think so
He's a lot cuter this way
All they know is he took out that last heavenly king
Which just leaves the demon lord to contend with
It just doesn't seem real to me though
Look a bar!
Sayo why don't we pop in for a bit?
You think we should dull our senses right before the biggest fight of our lives
I just thought we could take in the best of ambience
Like hearing and smelling drunks?
Besides there could be a brawl where someone gets stabbed to death with a broken bottle
So, hard pass
I've never met such a pathological worrywart
Come up and see me why don't ya
A bunny girl
Is your mom or dad a bunny?
What about going in there?
Casinos are always fun so what do you say?
I don't gamble
And frankly I'm surprised you'd assume any differently
Oh it could be worth it
There's actually a pretty good chance of getting some kind of awesome weapon or piece of gear if we win
Rista
If you truly think we can get a weapon that'll be effective against the demon lord as a prize in a casino
Then your brain must be the size of the little ball in the roulette wheel
You're one to talk about balls
The casino sounds pretty cool to me
Come on Saya
Having a tiny bit of fun isn't gonna hurt you know
Plus I think it would make Mosh and Elulu really happy
Our time would be better spent at a weapon shop
You're supposed to be a goddess
So why don't you think about the world a little more
I'm always thinking about it
Which is exactly why we need to take a breather
Oh please
It's really no wonder why Valkyrie told me that you were a third-rate goddess
Why are you bringing Valkyrie into this right now?
It's not like I don't already know that she's better than me
She's stronger, higher ranked, and even sexier
Let's calm down Rista
I am extremely calm
Hello sir
Are you interested in some greater medicinal herbs?
They have triple the effect and healing power of the regular kind
If you're lying about that I'll burn your shop down okay?
It's the truth
But I don't appreciate the threat
So do you want to buy some or not?
Hmm
I'll take a thousand
You don't need those
I mean I am a goddess with healing magic say
Hey!
My greater medicinal herbs are way better than any old restoration magic
No way!
My magic's a billion times stronger than your dumb herbs!
We'll see about that
Hey!
Come here man!
You look pretty beat up
I am
Had a run in with the demon lord's monsters earlier today
Scrapes on his arms look about the same
So why don't you and I have a race to see who can heal it quicker?
Eat my healing dust!
Let's go!
Yes!
Take flame to this man's world to cleanse it with my Megamon power!
Wow!
Those GMH healed me up insanely fast!
Fine I was!
Great job goddess of healing
Hey!
I'll take some of that GMH
Actually give me all that you have in there
Alright!
Thank you!
This is bull!
My magic is awesome!
It's okay Risto!
Try to relax!
You still have your little doll thing right?
No!
Shut up you stupid mushroom, mash, tater, whatever you are!
Hey!
It's not my fault you suck as a goddess!
Gosh!
That's too far!
You need to apologize to reach out!
Cut it out!
Just get going
Before we go in and see my father there's something I need to talk to you about
But first I want to know what happened to the legendary armor
It was eaten by a massive turtle
Say what?
It's not time for jokes!
Look I don't do jokes but the point is the thing doesn't exist anymore
But how could that have happened?
I'll spare you the details
What's done is done
Anyway what did you need to talk about?
Well it's about my father, the War Master
Wilkes Rosegard has been fighting off demons for over 30 years
Earlier this year as he was turning 80 he headed off to defeat the Demon Lord
But along the way and for unknown reasons he was turned into an infant
My men and I had to rescue him
Okay, is there some other point you're getting at?
My father doesn't have very long
The War Master is very respected throughout the land
I just want this time to be peaceful
Whenever he returned from battle he'd be tired
But he'd always pick me up and give me a pat on the head
He'd be so warm and loving
All I'm asking is if father says he wants to fight the Demon Lord alongside you
Please tell me that you'll persuade him not to
You don't need to ask me
Last thing I want is an old geezer slowing me down
Okay, I see
But please
Don't call him that
You have my thanks goddess and hero
I appreciate you coming here
After killing the heavenly king I don't remember what happened
But that aside
Now that the four heavenly kings are gone
Are you planning to attack the Demon Lord's castle?
I am
But I don't really need your help with that okay
I suppose that you don't
Why would you seek assistance from an old man?
Father
You've done more than your fair share already
The hero will finish what you've started
Indeed
Perhaps I could stay here and show the fair goddess around our legendary cathedral
Instead of trying to fight a young man's battle
I have an urgent message
Survivors from the Demon Lord's army are attacking the capital
I must go stop them at once
Father
I'll do it
You're the king after all
You should probably stick around the castle
But I
Don't sweat it pops
Just show the goddess your awesome cathedral or whatever
What the heck?
So now I'm just supposed to teeter around with baby grandpa?
Since you two have my stuff you should come with me
You should come with me
Oh yeah
Sure
Many years ago
I heard a legend about a goddess appearing to someone who'd save the world
I was so taken by it that I built this cathedral
I suppose I thought of myself as that hero
But now it seems that my role won't be so grand
Your people definitely see you as a hero
And you're much more heroic than a certain someone
Are you and your hero not getting along very well?
Just putting it mildly
You're so useless
You suck bro
Oh he's always putting me down
And it makes me want to punch his perfect face in
Oh I see
Sometimes the more talented a person is
The more twisted their personality can be
But let me ask you something
As a goddess
Are you aware of the reason why the gods are able to live eternally?
No all I really know is we can't die
The soul currently in your body is let's call it a virtual soul
Your real soul is stored in a room within the divine realm where time stands still
If you were to die in this world only your virtual soul would be affected
As long as a goddess's real soul is in the divine realm she will continue to live on forever
By the same principle if a summoned hero were to die he would simply return to his original world
Where his real soul remains safe from harm
You know a lot about this huh?
Well I've learned many things in this long life
In fact I've recently discovered there's a magical item that relates to this subject
Oh really? There is?
Yes
It is called chain destruction
A powerful and frightening thing
If it's used to destroy a virtual soul
It causes a chain reaction that eliminates the real soul as well
So if this item really does exist then Bosé and I could actually die for good?
Correct
I happen to know that the demon lord has already created a chain destruction
Not only that he successfully produced the ultimate weapon with which to apply it
A weapon that can shatter the soul of a hero and kill a goddess
I give you God Eater
A deity slaying sword
You are going to die dear goddess
As long as you're in this world the hero can escape to the divine realm at any time
I must block his retreat
But I don't understand
Why are you doing all this?
Odds because old age sucks
When I went on my journey to end the demon lord
I thought it would bring about my end as well
However the experience left me a changed man
The demon lord had seen through everything
He knew that my failure to realize my life's dream
Had cultivated a darkness deep inside my heart
His power was absolutely overwhelming
I found myself in complete awe
Like a newborn babe seeing the world for the first time
He had given me this rebirth
And now I worship the demon lord
The one who brings death as well as life
But since I once venerated you
I will show you mercy and make your death swift and painless
Well, well, such quick references
No!
No way!
This can't be happening
Are you afraid to die?
Even though you're a goddess
I suppose you're still a young girl
You poor scared creature
No!
Please!
Help me Seiya!
He can't
Now return to nothingness
Be gone
Seiya!
Oh man
Honestly
Kinda hate that we were mad the last time we saw each other
I can't believe my father would try to kill a goddess
Are you okay, Rista?
Rista said he shouldn't be trusted
It's you!
Well, I'm surprised you decided to show up here
Keep your creepy old hands away from her
I need her safe
Because if I didn't have Rista
I...
I wouldn't be able to go home
No!
Yeah, I guess that's true
Well, you alright?
What are you guys doing here?
Seiya said he was worried about you and made us come back to check
Huh?
Is that so?
Do you have some sort of precognitive ability, Hero?
All I can do is explore every last possibility
The hell does that mean?
What if that heavenly king, Eraser whatever, was faking his death?
Huh?
Or what if he really did die but then he came back as an angry ghost?
What if the demon lord has some weapon that can kill gods?
What if when he went to kill him he gave you the hypothetical god killing weapon?
And what if you had decided to use that weapon to kill the goddess so you could trap and kill me too?
Now, what if you, the war master, are my real enemy?
Whoa!
If that's his internal monologue then how does he sleep at night?
Oh well, that's nice say, yeah
And what if that goddess is some kind of imposter?
No, no! I'm the real deal!
So all this wasn't the result of logic or cunning or even intuition
You came back just because you're pathologically cautious
Father, please stop this!
Don't interfere, Rosalie
If you do, I will not hesitate to cut you down
Father...
It has been my lifelong dream
But the fact is, I was never destined to become the hero that saves the world
So I will simply have to take joy in being the one who slays that hero
Hush out!
That sword will kill you and destroy your soul back on earth!
You'll be dead dead!
Huh, I'll just have to kill him then
Mode, double eternal sword
Father!
Gross!
It seems that my frail old body is on the brink of withering away
If I can reclaim my former glory
I'll offer everything I have to the demon lord
Along with the God-heater sword
He gave me this demon spirit orb as well
Wait! So now he's a demon, Kim?
I must say this double eternal sword of yours is quite the formidable technique
Unpermidable technique.
However, I've already adjusted to it.
Style, evil light.
Eternal Sword X.
Oh, you defended yourself with just one sword.
I bet you've never really had your back
against the wall before, have you?
When did he pick up old Goth Goddess's ultimate move?
The Demon Lord told me something.
He said that the world you come from
is relatively peaceful,
and you don't know what war really is.
So, boy, I'll gladly show you
the sheer brutality of battle.
I wanted to save this for my fight with the Demon Lord.
What are you doing?
How friggin' heavy are those?
How the heck did you even find enough room
on your body to fit all of those things?
Spare Platinum Sword Plus, now!
Coming up!
This is gonna be hell on my arms, but oh well.
It's now time for Double Eternal Sword X!
Oh, since he took off those weights,
he should be hella fast!
This'll be a breeze!
So, you ready or you need a minute?
Well, actually, I do.
But I will be ready soon.
Mode Double Eternal Sword X,
Phoenix Blade Mech!
Let's go!
The attack game was just like even finished!
Who cares?
Stab his brains in, Zaya!
Engage style, Evil Light!
This is crazy!
Even my goddess eyes can't follow them!
But, I'm pretty sure Zaya has the upper hand!
You're strength is incredible!
But too bad for you, it's not enough.
I've adapted.
Eilolu!
You need to cast your quick spell to make Zaya even faster!
I can't!
Huh?
I've already casted on him!
I did it before the fight, because he's so cautious!
Oh no!
He's gonna be okay, isn't he?
He's gonna make it, right?
Of course he is!
He did say he was perfectly prepared, like always!
Uh oh!
He didn't say the damn catchphrase this time, did he?
Freesta!
I'll help him!
Me too!
We'll stop that demon!
Stay back!
You'll die!
Crushing Evil Light!
Zayna!
Your overabundance of caution and timidity
may have kept you alive for this long.
But you will not survive this fight on those traits alone.
Phoenix, thrust!
It won't be enough!
Are you learning, boy?
This is what it truly means to do battle.
And in this moment, you're frozen with pain and fear!
Zayna!
How can this be?
You should be crying out in pain.
Why are you not begging for mercy?
You may want to pretend that nothing's happened.
But without that arm, you have no chance of winning.
I'm not the only one here who's missing an arm, bro.
I use the 9th Valkyriesia, counter-break.
It takes a designated body part and returns any damage inflicted
back to where it came from.
I may have no sword.
I may have no sword, so I'll use my fist!
Phoenix, thrust!
I don't believe this.
What the hell is he?
He behaves like a warrior who's faced death time and time again!
Zayna!
Go on and fix my arm, Rista.
The herbs I bought won't be enough.
Zayna!
Yeah, of course I'll help.
That's gonna hurt pretty bad.
It hurts like hell.
At least I didn't pass out.
When you got that little scratch from the Reaper,
you made me heal you so fast.
You got all whiny then.
I thought you were soft as tofu.
You're missing the point, Rista.
Getting healed just means I have a better chance of winning.
Oh my god!
This feels like a million bees stung my shoulder.
You hear that?
Your old man's crying like a baby.
He doesn't deserve to be called my father.
Rista, go and heal the geezer's wound.
I guess I can do that.
Oh, my most humble thanks, fair goddess.
Okay, he's all healed up.
But uh...
Great.
That's it for us.
Rosalie's gotta take it from here.
He is not my responsibility.
He sold his soul to the demon lord and I was...
He's the shame of the kingdom.
He tried to kill the goddess and destroy the world.
If there's something you need him to know,
you're running out of time to tell him.
He tried to smear for us.
Certain people would.
You're running out of time.
You're running out.
Don't you think forever?
Yeah.
Pas more than they took out of time Daddy.
I'll wait from eggs in my eyes to eat.
Oh!
And to help it go forever.
I love you.
I love you again!
Yes, I'm sorry.
Father, I forgive you, so please, just this last time, pat my head like you used to.
Father.
My darling Rosalie, I love you very much.
Three days later, it was announced that Wolk's Roseguard, the mighty Warmaster, had passed away from old age.
The throne now belongs to Rosalie, who should make a pretty decent leader, as long as she keeps the barking to a minimum.
Thanks for everything, Seiya.
He okay?
Yeah, he's been asleep for a few days now.
He's fine. His wounds are totally healed.
You guys should stop worrying and go have some fun in the city.
Huh? Are you sure?
Yeah, check out the casino. You know this weirdo will just want to train.
Lisa?
I told you two to stop worrying. I think we can agree this guy who walks around like he's got a stick up his butt does enough of that for us.
When he wakes up from his little nap, I'll make sure he doesn't throw a fit.
After all, he is my lackey.
Look behind you.
I'm your what now?
Anyway, we need to talk about our plan before we go fight the Demon Lord.
Okay, everyone, listen carefully as our wise leader makes his big speech.
What about the casino?
How do you got mashed potatoes for brains, kid? This is the worst time for farting around like that.
I barely made it out alive from that War Master fight. That means I'm gonna have to train even harder if I really want to take down the Demon Lord.
Yeah, that's a great idea. You train your little heart out.
But before I start training, let's take a little time for some R&R.
Hold on a sec. What did you just say?
I said rest and relaxation. It won't be any big deal to take a couple days off.
You're saying we could go play around at the casino or something? Seriously?
Knock yourselves out.
That sounds amazing!
You've got to come with us, Seiya.
Yeah, I've earned some fun.
Seiya?
First, I'd like to look for some synthesis materials. But we can head out for some laughs later tonight.
Finally! I've been wanting to blow off some steam. I mean, we were due for an amusement park or beach or hot springs or just let our brains turn to jelly.
You know, we were always training, training, training, training, or fighting, fighting, fighting! But not today! We're gonna party ourself stupid!
Oh, yeah!